<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>learning on satinflame design</title>
    <link>https://www.satinflame.com/tags/learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in learning on satinflame design</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 09:44:31 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.satinflame.com/tags/learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HighEdWeb20 Golden Nuggets</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2020/10/high-ed-web-2020-golden-nuggets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 09:44:31 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2020/10/high-ed-web-2020-golden-nuggets/</guid>
      <description>Although 2020 has brought waves of isolation, it has also created the opportunity for more online conferences than ever.
After attending HighEdWeb&amp;rsquo;s Accessibility Summit in June, I was extremely excited to be able to attend my first HighEdWeb Annual Conference since 2014 (Portland, OR!)
We dove into the first day with a quick welcome and a round of lightning talks. The lightning talks were perfect for this platform—quick, 10-minute sessions about various topics to give you an overview of subjects you might want to delve into deeper afterward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knight University Case Study</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2019/09/knight-university-case-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 11:30:53 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2019/09/knight-university-case-study/</guid>
      <description>It was time for a redesign of Knight University, and while working through Designlab&amp;rsquo;s curriculum, I focused on creating a fresh web design with a focus on user needs. Knight University is for my experimental code/designs and is not a real university.
Before &amp;amp; after screenshots  The previous design for Knight University with an overly blue and less exciting design    The new design for Knight University    The open megamenu for the new design for Knight University   Case study Word file View an accessible version of the case study above</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apps and Tiny Tools</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2018/04/apps-and-tiny-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 15:13:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2018/04/apps-and-tiny-tools/</guid>
      <description>Game of LifeThe &#34;Game of Life&#34; is a small game based on a formula that determines whether a square is &#34;alive&#34; or &#34;dead&#34; based on its number of neighbors. React
Recipe CollectorA collection of delicous recipes--browse or add your own. The first five recipes are protected so they can&#39;t be deleted or modified.
ReactMongoDb
Escape from Toy FactoryA lot of fun putting together this JavaScript challenge--and it still has a little way to go!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OmniUpdate 2018 Training Conference</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2018/03/omniupdate-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 12:21:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2018/03/omniupdate-2018/</guid>
      <description>About the Conference OUTC is an annual conference targeted to new and existing users of OmniUpdate&amp;rsquo;s OU Campus system. If you&amp;rsquo;re not familiar, OU Campus is a CMS targeted towards higher education that provides a very powerful and extensible platform using XSLT.
It had been four years since I&amp;rsquo;d last attended a national conference, so I had a lot to learn. I was also excited to meet up with those who I had previously worked with during redesign projects and smaller updates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Turning Back: A Journey through Montana Code School</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2017/12/no-turning-back-montana-code-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 11:12:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2017/12/no-turning-back-montana-code-school/</guid>
      <description>My previous history included years of working as a front-end developer in higher education. It was hard to know what I&amp;rsquo;d get out of a 12-week bootcamp, but with a large amount of experience and self-study under my belt, I was ready to commit to finally getting the full exposure of modern web development. With 11 weeks behind me and only one week left, I wanted to share the journey so far.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
