<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>satinflame design</title>
    <link>https://www.satinflame.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on satinflame design</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 08:41:36 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.satinflame.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Retrieving Access to your Google Analytics Account</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2019/05/regain-access-google-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 08:41:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2019/05/regain-access-google-analytics/</guid>
      <description>If your site has a mysterious secondary Google Analytics number added to your website&amp;rsquo;s source code or you can&amp;rsquo;t find anyone at your school who seems to know the information for your Google Analytics setup, you may think that the existing information is now lost forever. However, there is one last measure you can try before giving up hope and creating a new Google Analytics account. First, be sure you can login to Google Analytics with the email you choose before requesting your email be added to the account in the following steps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shoreline Community College Redesign</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2019/02/shoreline-redesign/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 10:23:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2019/02/shoreline-redesign/</guid>
      <description>In January 2018, Shoreline unveiled an updated Identity Guideline which I implemented from the original PDF into an interactive Identity Guidelines webpage. (As an reminder, it is a best practice—as noted by Jakob Nielsen—to use HTML instead of PDF for online presentations.) In addition to structuring the content to be responsive regardless of device, I added hex codes to each color block and made them clickable so a user could easily copy the color codes to their clipboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding Bar Graphs using Highcharts in OU Campus</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2018/09/bar-graph-highcharts-ou-campus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 18:47:58 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2018/09/bar-graph-highcharts-ou-campus/</guid>
      <description>In this example, the HTML table is transformed using the Highcharts library—it is free for non-profits, so go grab a Highcharts Non-commercial license.
On your page, include the Highcharts library file as well as your customized JS—specific to this type of bar graph setup. In your file at /_resources/ou/editor/wysiwyg.css or similar, add the following CSS to show the table in edit mode only:
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8  #datatable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apps and Tiny Tools</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2018/04/apps-and-tiny-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 15:13:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2018/04/apps-and-tiny-tools/</guid>
      <description>Game of Life The &#34;Game of Life&#34; is a small game based on a formula that determines whether a square is &#34;alive&#34; or &#34;dead&#34; based on its number of neighbors. React
    Recipe Collector A collection of delicous recipes--browse or add your own. The first five recipes are protected so they can&#39;t be deleted or modified.
ReactMongoDb
    Escape from Toy Factory A lot of fun putting together this JavaScript challenge--and it still has a little way to go!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OmniUpdate 2018 Training Conference</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2018/03/omniupdate-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 12:21:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2018/03/omniupdate-2018/</guid>
      <description>About the Conference OUTC is an annual conference targeted to new and existing users of OmniUpdate&amp;rsquo;s OU Campus system. If you&amp;rsquo;re not familiar, OU Campus is a CMS targeted towards higher education that provides a very powerful and extensible platform using XSLT.
It had been four years since I&amp;rsquo;d last attended a national conference, so I had a lot to learn. I was also excited to meet up with those who I had previously worked with during redesign projects and smaller updates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a Progress Bar in OU Campus</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2018/01/progress-bar-in-omniupdate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 14:03:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2018/01/progress-bar-in-omniupdate/</guid>
      <description>Overview This code demo available on GitHub allows you to create a loading progress bar that is managed from a table transformation within OmniUpdate&amp;rsquo;s OU Campus. The CSS and JavaScript must be added into your page either by including it into your global files or making a separate call to each. The jQuery library must be loaded prior to calling the JavaScript code. Developers: If you add on any helpful additions, please make a Pull Request!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Turning Back: A Journey through Montana Code School</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2017/12/no-turning-back-montana-code-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 11:12:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2017/12/no-turning-back-montana-code-school/</guid>
      <description>My previous history included years of working as a front-end developer in higher education. It was hard to know what I&amp;rsquo;d get out of a 12-week bootcamp, but with a large amount of experience and self-study under my belt, I was ready to commit to finally getting the full exposure of modern web development. With 11 weeks behind me and only one week left, I wanted to share the journey so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up A Multi Website Magento Store</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2017/03/setting-up-a-multi-website-magento-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 09:37:25 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2017/03/setting-up-a-multi-website-magento-store/</guid>
      <description>Last year I had the opportunity to learn about working in the e-commerce platform Magento–creating products, adding modules, updating security patches and more. Though there is a lot to learn, understanding the file structure of Magento was essential in order to migrate another store (running version 1.4) into a multi-website for another store that had been recently upgraded to 1.9.2. While searching for the best process, I learned there are many ways to set up a second store on the same Magento install—but there were many things I still didn’t understand being the novice server administer of a one-person web team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speeding Up Load Times on Magento CE 1.9x</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2016/07/speeding-up-load-times-on-magento-ce-1-9x2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 19:37:25 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2016/07/speeding-up-load-times-on-magento-ce-1-9x2/</guid>
      <description>While this entry could also be aptly named OMG How Do I Make Pages Load Faster in Magento?, I’ve finally found a solution to speeding up my Magento website that makes me so much less bitter, I can now even think semi-straight. If you’re searching for answers as well–and perhaps not finding adequate solutions–I hope this post will be of value for learning all the different ways to increase your Magento website’s performance!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Migration Refinement For Horry Georgetown Technical College</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2016/07/content-migration-refinement-for-horry-georgetown-technical-college/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 15:02:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2016/07/content-migration-refinement-for-horry-georgetown-technical-college/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes redesigns need to happen fast! If your web team is small or needs a helping hand in preparing your website ready for its big unveil, consider contacting me for information on how I can help!
For this project, I worked with Missy at Horry Georgetown Technical College to help her quickly release the migration of her new beautiful redesign out into the “wild!”
I contributed in the following ways:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giant Decline in Bounce Rate: Is it Really a Good Thing?</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2016/06/giant-decline-in-bounce-rate-is-it-really-a-good-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2016 19:57:25 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2016/06/giant-decline-in-bounce-rate-is-it-really-a-good-thing/</guid>
      <description>Is it Really a Good Thing?
No, probably not.
In April 2016, I updated a website with a fresh, responsive Magento design in collaboration with Social Ruckus in Bozeman, Montana. There was a noticeable slowing of the websites as most features used AJAX and dynamic loading. Even so, I noticed a huge drop (~50% to 3%) in bounce rate. Bounce dropped after releasing RWD&amp;ndash;I&amp;rsquo;m a bit nervous. What other metrics should I look at?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Explore Montana State University</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2016/04/explore-montana-state-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 15:02:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2016/04/explore-montana-state-university/</guid>
      <description>In 2015, I had the pleasure of implementing a university lead generation form designed by Graphic Designer Ron Lambert and the Montana State University marketing team!
Overall this design was challenging due to a few of our special page requirements:
Keep the users on the lead page In order to get the contact information we hoped for, we had to include enough content to remain informative without linking to other pages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Residence Life Interactive Map</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2016/03/residence-life-interactive-map/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 15:02:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2016/03/residence-life-interactive-map/</guid>
      <description>When looking into how best to create an image with interactive elements, I had to go beyond using outdated image maps and get creative with implementing maps using SVG (Scalable Vector Graphics) and creating a responsive, interactive information pop-ups!
This map looks great on desktop and mobile—test it out yourself! The functionality enables a user to click either the name or the building itself to learn more about it.
Within Illustrator, we grouped paths and then was able to edit the exported .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Steps to Improving your Amazon Business Catalog [List]</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2016/03/3-steps-to-improving-your-amazon-business-catalog-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 19:57:25 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2016/03/3-steps-to-improving-your-amazon-business-catalog-list/</guid>
      <description>Regardless if you’ve been handed an inventory of products you know nothing about, or if you’ve been maintaining your catalog for years, there may be a few things you haven’t considered when managing your products.
Although there are many resources to choose from within Amazon’s Vendor Central Resource Center, the following actions are some simple ways to improve the findability of your products:
Create variation families If you have many items with similar features, be sure your customer can see them all immediately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Naropa University</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2016/01/naropa-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2016 15:02:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2016/01/naropa-university/</guid>
      <description>Working with the team from OmniUpdate along with Mary Haste from Naropa University, we implemented a redesign for the entire university website.
Unlike other designs I’ve implemented, Naropa University’s wasn’t quite ready to move all pages into the responsive view. We worked through the challenges and created non-responsive and responsive versions using the same Sass-based CSS. As they work through updating each page’s outdated elements—removing fixed width content, updating low-quality images with higher-resolution versions and revisiting text—they can then easily switch their page to the responsive version using a page setting in the OmniUpdate CMS!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth City State University Web Redesign</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2016/01/elizabeth-city-state-university-web-redesign/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2016 15:02:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2016/01/elizabeth-city-state-university-web-redesign/</guid>
      <description>ECSU Secondary Page      ECSU Homepage      ECSU Admissions      ECSU History Page    
In 2015, I worked with Vayakone Sphabmixay from SAX, Inc. implementing their redesign for Elizabeth City State University in North Carolina. There were many creative design pieces that presented fun challenges for implementing in a responsive environment.
Historical Year Timeline The timeline is both collapsible and adapts to mobile devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northeastern University’s College of Professional Students</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2016/01/cps-neu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2016 15:02:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2016/01/cps-neu/</guid>
      <description>In the summer of 2014, I had the opportunity to develop the code for a design created by the team at I-SITE, INC. for the College of Professional Students in Boston, MA. Unlike new development work, this redesign required an update to the base code using only minimal CSS.
Before updating, this Web page had used mobile queries to (unfortunately) simply hide the “unnecessary” mobile elements to make the content disappear on smaller devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Jeanine Schoessler, Front-End Web Developer Jeanine enjoys crafting web experiences for higher education. Her passions include listening to music, supporting others on their journey to learn web development, and visiting every aircraft museum she and her husband can find. Recently, she has become an active member of FourCornerz Toastmasters. In 2015, she graduated from the Leadership MSU program and was nominated for MSU Employee of the Year. In 2018, she was named one of freeCodeCamp&amp;rsquo;s top 200 contributors and became an Official Partner for OmniUpdate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/contact/</guid>
      <description> Contact Me  Follow me on Twitter and send a quick hello
 View my experience at Linkedin Browse through my current Github or Codepen projects  Send me a quick message to learn more about updating your site, or visit my portfolio to see my completed projects!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/faq/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stock Photos</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/stock-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/stock-photos/</guid>
      <description>Stock Photos Photos I’ve taken that can be used freely in any lawful use:
 in digital format on websites, blog posts, social media, advertisements, film and television productions, web and mobile applications in printed materials such as magazines, newspapers, books, brochures, flyers, product packaging for decorative use in your home, office or any public place personal use or commercial use    mountains in Montana      Sikorksy UH-60      chocolate cake      Glacier National Park sun shining through treetops      patio set in Cancun      hummingbird at a feeder</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>