<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bootstrap4 on satinflame design</title>
    <link>https://www.satinflame.com/tags/bootstrap4/</link>
    <description>Recent content in bootstrap4 on satinflame design</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 11:20:06 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.satinflame.com/tags/bootstrap4/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>OU Campus Components vs. Snippets</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2019/07/oucampus-components-vs-snippets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 11:20:06 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2019/07/oucampus-components-vs-snippets/</guid>
      <description>For years, managing advanced features within OU Campus has been handled using a variety of snippets and assets. As a reminder, snippets come in two versions: 1) an inserted chunk of code or text that will be manually edited and managed and 2) table-transformations, which will be the majority of the examples for this article. Assets, similarly, can be used to manage a chunk of code, text, form, or collection of photos within a page; however, since each asset is centrally updated, every instance of one asset points to one source.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shoreline Community College Redesign</title>
      <link>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2019/02/shoreline-redesign/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 10:23:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.satinflame.com/blog/2019/02/shoreline-redesign/</guid>
      <description>In January 2018, Shoreline unveiled an updated Identity Guideline which I implemented from the original PDF into an interactive Identity Guidelines webpage. (As an reminder, it is a best practice—as noted by Jakob Nielsen—to use HTML instead of PDF for online presentations.) In addition to structuring the content to be responsive regardless of device, I added hex codes to each color block and made them clickable so a user could easily copy the color codes to their clipboard.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
